A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Commissioner of the Virginia Dept. of Labor and Industry, 1947-2010
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 34698], 1977-1990., Extent: 4.35 cu. ft. (5 boxes). (Box 1-5)
  - Supradur Manufacturing Company, 1989 (Box 4)
  - VCU, 1985-1990 (Box 4)
  - VOSH Benchmarks, 1983-1986 (Box 4)
  - VOSH CASPA's, 1987 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Directors meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Virginia State Plan, 1984-1987 (Box 5)
- Series V: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 35638], 1971-1992., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box 1-2)
  - Accounts Receivable Study, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Associated General Contractors of Virginia, 1971-1991 (Box 1)
  - Boiler and Pressure Vessel Division, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of, 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - Ergonomics, 1990-1991 (Box 1)
  - Fourth Street Office Building, Remodel - Renovation, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1988-1991 (Box 1)
  - Health Enforcement, 1991-1992 (Box 1)
  - Labor law, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, 1988-1992 (Box 2)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, Publications, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Memorandums (Inter-Office), 1986-1992 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987-1992 (Box 2)
  - News clippings, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
- Series VI: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 37903], 1986-1997., Extent: 9 cu. ft. (9 boxes). (Box 1-9)
  - Administration, Division of, 1991-1994 (Box 1)
  - AFL-CIO, Virginia, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Agency Level Information, 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Agency Policy Statements, 1987-1993 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship, Council Members, 1988-1995 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship, Dorey Electric, 1990-1993 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship Related Instruction, 1990-1994 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
  - Attorney General's Office, 1991-1993 (Box 1)
  - Bungee jumping, Rules and regulations, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bungee jumping, Rules and regulations, 1992-1993 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, Labor Law, 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, Staff Meetings, 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, Weekly reports, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Comptroller's Office, 1986-1992 (Box 2)
  - Data Processing, 1986-1990 (Box 3)
  - Defense Conversion Task Force, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Dorey Electric, 1993-1996 (Box 3)
  - Economic Development (Framme), 1993 (Box 3)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1992-1994 (Box 3)
  - Enforcement Policy, Division of, 1990-1994 (Box 3)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1989-1993 (Box 3)
  - Gas Pipeline Safety, 1993 (Box 3)
  - General Services, Department of, 1989-1994 (Box 3)
  - Goals and Objectives, 1989-1994 (Box 3)
  - Governor's Employment and Training Department, 1986-1993 (Box 3)
  - Grant issues, 1990-1992 (Box 3)
  - Grant issues, 1993-1995 (Box 3)
  - Health enforcement, 1993-1996 (Box 4)
  - HCCA (Heavy Construction Contractors Association), 1990-1994 (Box 4)
  - House Bills, 1992-1994 (Box 4)
  - Industrial Commission, 1987-1992 (Box 4)
  - Information requests, 1985-1994 (Box 4)
  - Information Management, Council of, 1989-1995 (Box 4)
  - Information Policy Board, 1989-1993 (Box 4)
  - Information Technology, Department of, 1991-1995 (Box 4)
  - IDSS (Integrated Decision Support System), 1990-1992 (Box 4)
  - JLARC (Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission), 1991-1995 (Box 4)
  - Job Accompany Program, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, CAM (Consultation Activity Measures) Report, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, Federal-State Operations, 1995 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, 1991-1995 (Box 5)
  - Labor Law, 1995 (Box 5)
  - Leadership Council, 1993-1995 (Box 5)
  - Legislation, 1991-1995 (Box 5)
  - Legislative, 1991-1995 (Box 6)
  - Lockout-Tagout, Task Force, Interim Order for Virginia Power, 1988-1991 (Box 6)
  - Migrant seasonal farm workers, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Minority business enterprises, 1988-1992 (Box 6)
  - Mosher Steel Court case, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
  - NAGLO (National Association of Governmental Labor Organizations), 1990-1992 (Box 6)
  - National Governor's Association, 1990 (Box 6)
  - NIOSH (National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health), 1990-1992 (Box 7)
  - OSHA Reform Act, 1991-1993 (Box 7)
  - OSHSPA, 1990-1995 (Box 7)
  - Overhead High Voltage Line Safety Act, 1989-1995 (Box 7)
  - Petrochemical Industries, 1990-1993 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1993-1996 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Policy Analyses, 1989-1992 (Box 7)
  - Project Streamline Initiative, 1990-1994 (Box 7)
  - Quarterly Briefings, DLI, 1990-1992 (Box 7)
  - Research and Statistics, 1990-1993 (Box 7)
  - Richmond Coalition Against Drugs, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
  - Richmond Newspaper vs. Commonwealth of Virginia, 1989-1990 (Box 7)
  - Rural Economic Development Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 8)
  - Safety Enforcement Division, 1994-1997 (Box 8)
  - Safety and Health Codes Board, 1992-1996 (Box 8)
  - Safety Week, 1990 (Box 8)
  - School To Work Transition Program, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Secretary's Excellance Award, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Senate Bills, 1989-1994 (Box 8)
  - S.G. Communications (WTVR Tower), 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Small Business Administration, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Social services, Dept. of, 1989-1993 (Box 8)
  - State Plan Activities Measures Reports (SPAM), 1986-1991 (Box 8)
  - Surveys, 1987-1993 (Box 8)
  - Trenching and Excavation Standards, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Underground Storage Tank, 1990 (Box 8)
  - Union Information, 1992-1997 (Box 8)
  - Virginia Liaison Office, 1984-1996 (Box 8)
  - Waste Management, Dept. of, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Weekly Reports, Commissioner's Office, 1997 (Box 9)
- Series VII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 41036], 1989-2000., Extent: 5 cu. ft. (5 boxes). (Box 1-5)
  - Asbestos, 1991-1993 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship related instruction, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship Division, 1995-1998 (Box 1)
  - Attorney General's Office, 1994-1997 (Box 1)
  - Commissioner's Office, Memos and Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 1)
  - Weekly report files for retention, 1996-1997 (Box 1)
  - Blue Ridge Safety Network, 1993-1997 (Box 1)
  - Child Labor Law Study, 1991-1993 (Box 1)
  - Commissioner's Office, Memos and Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, NESHAP (National Emissions Standards for Hazardous Air Pollutants) Federal and State Regulations, 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, OSHA Strategic Plan, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, Speeches (Theron J. Bell), 1994-1998 (Box 2)
  - Commissioner's Office, John Mills Barr files, 1998-2000 (Box 2)
  - Health Enforcement, 1997-1999 (Box 2)
  - Labor law files, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Labor law files, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Labor law files, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Labor law files, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Labor law files, Wallops Island, 1990-1999 (Box 3)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, Comprehensive Evaluation Report, 1995-1997 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Department of, Interim Evaluation Report, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - Mandate assessments, 1994-1999 (Box 4)
  - Migrant and Seasonal Farm workers Board, 1996-1999 (Box 4)
  - Migrant Workers Policy Committee, 1989-1998 (Box 4)
  - Office of Legal Support (formerly PETS), 1994-1998 (Box 4)
  - Safety Enforcement, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Safety Enforcement, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Variances, 1994-1998 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Consultation Program, 1994-1998 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Cooperative Compliance Program, 1995-1998 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Legal, 1993-1995 (Box 5)
  - VOSH Voluntary Protection, 1992-1999 (Box 5)
  - Worker's Compensation Commission, 1992-1999 (Box 5)
- Series VIII: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 42488], 1983-2002., Extent: 4 cu. ft. (4 boxes). (Box 1-4)
  - Accident reports, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
  - Agency Level Information, 1990-1999 (Box 1)
  - American Society of Safety Engineers, Newsletters, 1988-1998 (Box 1)
  - Apprenticeship issues, 1997-1999 (Box 1)
  - Asbestos, 1993-2001 (Box 1)
  - Bloodborne Pathogens Standards Information, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
  - Budget issues, 1991-2000 (Box 1)
  - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1993-1999 (Box 1)
  - CFOI (Census of Fatal Occupational Injuries), 1998 (Box 1)
  - Child Labor Regulations, 1992-1994 (Box 1)
  - CVC (Combined Virginia Campaign), 1991-2000 (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, 1995-1999 (Box 1)
  - Commerce and Trade, Weekly report submittals, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
  - Commissioner's files (Jeffrey D. Brown), 1998-2002 (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth Management Institute, 1989-1995 (Box 1)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of, 1996-1998 (Box 2)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 1993-1996 (Box 2)
  - Conflict of Interest Act, 1983-1995 (Box 2)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1998-2001 (Box 2)
  - Emergency Services, Office of, 1991-2001 (Box 2)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Office of, 1988-1998 (Box 2)
  - Environment, Council of, 1990-1992 (Box 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1987-2001 (Box 2)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, Advisory Committee 1998 (Box 2)
  - Ergonomics, 1993-2000 (Box 2)
  - Fatality reports and statistics, 1985-1999 (Box 2)
  - Field Operations Manual revisions, 1989-2000 (Box 2)
  - Field Sanitation Standard, 1987-2000 (Box 2)
  - Fire Programs, Dept. of, 1989-1991 (Box 2)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1996-2000 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office, Correspondence (Governor George Allen Administration), 1994-1997 (Box 2)
  - Governor's Office, Correspondence (Governor Douglas Wilder Administration), 1989-1994 (Box 3)
  - Health enforcement, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1987-1996 (Box 3)
  - Human Resources, 1996-1999 (Box 3)
  - Labor Law, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Labor Law, Public Utility (GTE, AT & T), 1992 (Box 3)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, OSHSPA, 1996-2001 (Box 4)
  - Labor, U.S. Dept. of, Publications, 2000-2001 (Box 4)
  - Mandate Assessments, 2000-2001 (Box 4)
  - Misc. correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 4)
  - NIOSH (National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health), 1993-1999 (Box 4)
  - VCU (Virginia Commonwealth University), Virginia Labor Studies Center, 1992-2000 (Box 4)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1994-2001 (Box 4)
  - VOSH (Virginia Occupational Safety and Health Program), Evaluations, 1992-1996 (Box 4)
  - VOSH, Safety Enforcement correspondence, 2000 (Box 4)
- Series IX: Correspondence and subject files [Accession 50380], 1972-2010., Extent: 14 cu. ft. (14 boxes). (Box 1-14)
  - Chronological files, 1972-1978 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1992 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1996 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Chronological files, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 January (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 February (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 March (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 April (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 May (Box 2)
  - Chronological files, 2001 June (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 July (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 August (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 September (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 October (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 November (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2001 December (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 January (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 February (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 March (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 April (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 May (Box 3)
  - Chronological files, 2002 May (Box 4)
  - Chronological files, 2002 June (Box 4)
  - Chronological files, 2002 July (Box 4)
  - Chronological files, 2002 August (Box 4)
  - Chronological files, 2002 September (Box 5)
  - Chronological files, 2002 October (Box 5)
  - Chronological files, 2002 November (Box 5)
  - Chronological files, 2002 December (Box 5)
  - Chronological files, 2003 January (Box 5)
  - Chronological files, 2003 January (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 February (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 March (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 April (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 May (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 June (Box 6)
  - Chronological files, 2003 July (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2003 August (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2003 September (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2003 October (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2003 November (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2003 December (Box 7)
  - Chronological files, 2004 January (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 February (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 March (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 April (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 May (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 June (Box 8)
  - Chronological files, 2004 July (Box 9)
  - Chronological files, 2004 August (Box 9)
  - Chronological files, 2004 September (Box 9)
  - Chronological files, 2004 October (Box 9)
  - Chronological files, 2004 November (Box 9)
  - Chronological files, 2004 December (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 January (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 February (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 March (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 April (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 May (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 June (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 July 1-15 (Box 10)
  - Chronological files, 2005 July 16-31 (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2005 August (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2005 September (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2005 October (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2005 November (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2005 December (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 January (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 February (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 March (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 April (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 May (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 June (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 July (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 August (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 September 3-21 (Box 11)
  - Chronological files, 2006 September 22-30 (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2006 October (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2006 November (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2006 December (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 January (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 February (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 March (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 April (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 May (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 June (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 July (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 August (Box 12)
  - Chronological files, 2007 September (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2007 October (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2007 November (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2007 December (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 January (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 February (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 March (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 April (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 May (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 June (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 July (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 August (Box 13)
  - Chronological files, 2008 September (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2008 October (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2008 November (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2008 December (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 January (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 February (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 March (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 April (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 May (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 June (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 July (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 August (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 September (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 October (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 November (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2009 December (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2010 January (Box 14)
  - Chronological files, 2010 February (Box 14)